<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<npcs totalentries ="11">
   <npc name="" entries="1">
      <speach>The last keeper, Trina, walks throughout a major city while being escorted by armed guards. Suddenly, a mysterious figure runs by Trina, stealing her coin purse. The guards begin to chase the mysterious figure.</speach>
</npc>
	  <npc name = "Guard" entries ="1">
	  <speach>Kid, get back here!</speach>
</npc>
	  <npc name = "" entries ="1">
      <speach>Eventually, they corner the thief into an alleyway. The thief fights the guards and they are defeated. Trina approaches the alleyway.</speach>
</npc>
	  <npc name = "Trina" entries ="1">
	  <speach>Boy, are you homeless?</speach>
   </npc>
  <npc name = "????" entries ="1">
	  <speach>That is none of your concern. Stay back and leave me be!</speach>
   </npc>
  <npc name = "Trina" entries ="1">
	  <speach>Now.Now. Don't worry I am not going to harm you. I wanted to offer you a proposition. Since, you dispatched my personal guards, I know that you can fight. So how about you become a personal guard of mine?</speach>
   </npc>
  <npc name = "????" entries ="1">
	  <speach>But I just stole money from you. Why are you being so kind to me?</speach>
   </npc>
  <npc name = "Trina" entries ="1">
	  <speach>If you begin to question why someone does something or why they dont, the world can become a very complex place. I know that you are starving and that you were desperate to get food. Stealing from me was a known way to get money. Now what is your answer?</speach>
   </npc>
  <npc name = "????" entries ="1">
	  <speach>Sure, I will become your body guard.</speach>
   </npc>
  <npc name = "" entries ="1">
	  <speach>The boy hands the coin purse to Trina and helps the guards to their feet. Trina and company return back to her home in the city.</speach>
   </npc>
  <npc name = "" entries ="1">
	  <speach>Since then years have gone by and the boy had grown stronger as a person and as a bodyguard as a result from his training.</speach>
   </npc>
</npcs>